Fang life along the way melody we have
[music]
play so hello guy welcome back to my new
video I hope you all are doing well
so guys for a long time none of our
videos were getting uploaded on the channel the
reason for which was our bike had met with an accident
once there was an accident in
which there was not much damage
but guys this time my friend had taken the bike
so the bike met with an accident the bike had a
lot of damage due to which I had to
put the bike on claim I am going to share with you all the
things about the bike today, what all
damages were done to the bike and brother
what documents are required if you have to pay the
claim
watch the video till the end I will
give you all the information if your bike meets with an accident
then how do you have to take a claim
what documents do you have to take
we will share all the things if you are new to the channel then
go and subscribe to the channel brother
and watch the video till the end and
brother if you like any video related to 350  If you
want to see it, you can go to our channel and
see it related to mileage
and its problems, causes, causes, A to Z.
You will find almost all the topics. I have
made videos on almost all the topics, so if you want to
see any video related to Hunter, then
you can go and watch the channel and brother, do
subscribe. Now I will
tell you all the things about it,
what documents are required for the claim,
I will tell you that and clear it for you and
what all things you have to keep in mind
because at the time of claim, some frauds happen with you which you do
not know about,
so I will tell you all the things
in this video. If you have insurance from outside, then do
not take anything from outside. If there is a
claim, then you must put it on the claim
because many of its parts are very costly.
So you can see the condition of the bike, it is
absolutely new. When the
accident happened, there was a lot of
damage to the rest of the bike. Brother, let
me make one thing clear to you, the bike
looks sporty, it runs very well, it will be enough to
drive you.  You will definitely feel like it,
but let me make one thing clear to you,
this is not a sports bike because the
friend who met with the accident was my
friend, so he was probably driving the bike too fast
because this is not a sports bike,
if you use it like a sports bike then
it will definitely betray you somewhere, so
after all this is a Royal Enfield
bike, the more
you ride it at a speed of 50-60, the more you ride the bike straight, the better it will be
for you, this is a very
good bike, it will last for a long time and will serve
you for a long time, so brother, now let
us talk about what
parts of it were damaged
in the accident, we will show you all those parts
and what all has changed, so brother, let us talk about
its front, you
can see its headlight in the front, the headlight was completely
broken, the headlight has been completely changed, but
I did not understand one thing, the headlight has
changed, this is the thing that you are seeing on its side,
I will zoom in and show you, you are
seeing this, see there is a scratch in it,
these are all the things you have to see carefully  You have to keep in mind
that these people change some things in the claim
and do not change some things, like
my indicator was broken, they changed the indicator, there was no
such work in the brake, the
brake was fine, there was no such problem in the brake and
brother, you have to take care of these things only, if anything is
changed then you have to
look at all the things carefully, there was the brake lever, the
handle was complete, the brake levers were on both sides, the
handle had become completely crooked, so all these
things get changed, the
things that you see from the top, these people change all of them,
but there are some things
inside which people
manage with the old ones, now what is this, why is it so, the
company people know, but I will show you the things and
tell you, so that if
this happens to you for the first time, if by chance an
accident happens, then you have to take
care of these things there and here
both the upper covers of the silencer, the
front and the back, both of them were changed,
both of them had got a lot of scratches and had
also become crooked, nothing had happened to the silencer inside,
so only its cover of the silencer was
changed, the rest  The brake on the right side and
your brake here was completely
broken, so look at this also, yours has been
replaced but it has been completely replaced, there is a scratch in half of
its pedal, the brake pedal has been changed
but I don't know the upper part of it,
why it was not changed, they say that
brother, when the bank people come to inspect, then only the thing which is
completely broken is
replaced, the rest is not changed
and you get a claim for only one side,
my gear lever on the left side was
crooked, so they straightened it and
put it back in place, so let's
tell the story of one side, let's understand the
story of the other side, the
things which should have been changed here,
they did not change them completely and
this was our panel on which your Hunter 350
badging is given, it was completely scratched
and it was also broken, so
they replaced it with a new one too, so here brother,
you have to see all these things, when you
go to pick up the vehicle and when you go to put it in, first
make a video and click a good photo
so that you keep in mind what things you have done
here  I had given it for repair so that when you
pick up the car, you should know whether the things that
you had asked to be repaired were done
properly or
not, what kind of work has been done on it,
rest of your accessories, if they are
included in your insurance, then you will get a
claim for it, otherwise you will not get it,
like my Apple Guard, this
was also completely bolted but I did not get any claim for it
and here I
also had an after market ladies footer,
which had also become crooked, so
I got it straightened and let me tell you that
along with that, whatever accessories you have installed after market
and whatever accessories you have installed from the showroom, if the
accessories from the showroom
are included in your insurance, then you will
get a claim for that, rest
you will not get any claim on any after market accessories,
talking about the rest, the meter
was left there, brother, its meter is very
weak anyway, if you
even keep your hand on it properly, according to me, it will
break, so I always
talk about the meter, so take care of it brother, always
talk about it and what all documents we need there
If
we talk about the documents required here, then here
you will need Aadhar card, PAN card and the RC of the vehicle,
insurance will be required and your
DL will be required, a
photocopy of all these things is required, after that the
bank from which you have insurance,
like I had ICICI insurance,
so according to them, whoever comes, the
bank people check it and go in two or three days,
then they do their further
process, then your payment is done,
then whatever parts are broken in yours, the
company installs them and
fits them, then you will get a call from the company
that your vehicle is ready, and let me
tell you that sometimes it takes time
because some parts are not available in the company,
if there is any such part
which is not available in rare then it takes some
time, so this further
delays you a little, the rest, it took maximum
10 to 12 days for your vehicle to be ready, so it takes maximum 10 to 12 days for me, 10 to 12 days.
You will get the car in 10 to 12 days, so brother,
drive the car very safely, definitely wear a helmet,
I have removed the glasses,
I will install the mirrors, I know it is for safety features,
so brother, definitely take care of safety,
no one should get into an accident,
brother, you also get hurt in an accident, the bike
also gets damaged, so let's go
son, you should not get hurt,
like my friend had an accident,
he got badly injured, so brother, there is
no need to drive the bike because this is
not a sports bike, because if you
lose control of it, then you will definitely get into an
accident, so there is
no need to make many turns, just ride the bike comfortably, it will
give good mileage, it is a good bike, it is
very good, you will enjoy riding it,
drive it at a speed of 40-50, the rest is not
that it does not run, everything is there brother, it has a 350 cc
engine, so you can drive it however you want,
but according to me, you should
drive it normally, drive it like a bullet,
you will enjoy driving it and you will also be safe,
so guy  Please do tell me by commenting how you liked the video
and now my videos
will come regularly, my bike has arrived, so if
you want any topic related to Hunter, then please tell me by commenting,
I will cover that topic also,
do tell me by commenting how you liked the rest of the video
and like the video, do subscribe to the channel brother, so
brother, we will meet
in the new video, enjoy the video,
soon you will get to see our new video on the channel,
so brother, I will tell the channel once
again, please subscribe to the channel,
your support is
very important for me, it is very important, thank you very
much